I had a dream
We were sipping whisky neat
Highest floor, the bowery
And I was high enough
'Somewhere along the lines
We stopped seeing eye to eye
You were staying out all night
And I had enough
No, I don't wanna know where
you been or where you're going
But I know I won't be home
And you'll be on your own
Who's gonna walk you through
the dark side of the morning?
Who's gonna rock you when the
sun won't let you sleep?
Who's waking up to drive you
home when you're drunk and all
alone?
Who's gonna walk you through
the dark side of the morning?
It ain't me
I had a dream
We were back to seventeen
Summer nights and the liberties
Never growing up
I'll take with me the
polaroids and the memories
But you know I'm gonna leave
behind the worst of us
Who's gonna walk you through
the dark side of the morning?
Who's gonna rock you when the
sun won't let you sleep?
Who's waking up to drive you
home when you're drunk and all
alone?
Who's gonna walk you through
the dark side of the morning?
It ain't me, no no
Who's gonna walk you through
the dark side of the morning?
It ain't me
www.RentAnAdviser.com