I used to believe
We were burnin' on the edge of
somethin' beautiful
Somethin' beautiful
Sellin' a dream
Smoke and mirrors keep us
waiting on a miracle
On a miracle
Say, go through the darkest of days
Heaven's a heartbreak away
Never let you go, never let me down
Oh, it's been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go, never let me down
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
Don't fall asleep
At the wheel, we've got a
million miles ahead of us
Miles ahead of us
All that we need
Is a rude awakening to know
we're good enough
Know we're good enough
Say go through the darkest of days
Heaven's a heartbreak away
Never let you go, never let me down
Oh, it's been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go, never let me down
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
Don't you give up, nah-nah-nah
I won't give up, nah-nah-nah
Let me love you
www.RentAnAdviser.com